All right, we'll call to order the Miami Special Utilities Authority
built board meeting for Tuesday, May 19th, 2026.
We'll have the invocation by Deacon of All Saints Church Ms. K Bowman Harvey.
Let us pray.
Oh God, you made us in your own image and redeemed us through Jesus your Son.
Look with compassion on the whole human family.
Take away the arrogance and hatred which infect our hearts.
Break down the walls that separate us.
Unite us in bonds of love.
And work through our struggle and confusion to accomplish your purposes on Earth.
That in your good time all nations and races may serve you in harmony around your heavenly
throne through Jesus Christ our Lord.
Amen.
For public input unscheduled personal appearances.
Five A claims list.
Five B minutes from the May 5th, 2026 regular meeting.
Motion to approve.
Aye.
Five C, budget amendment 2610,
receding and expending loan funds to build the fiber and advanced metering infrastructure.
Crystal.
So this is kind of the final step of putting the money into place in the line items and
how it will be spent and just receding those loan funds into our accounting system.
When are we going to start?
Finalize the AMI contract and we are materials on order for fiber.
Cool.
We're close.
Good.
I think a motion will be approved.
Aye.
Barnes.
Jones.
Aye.
Dunkel.
Parker.
Aye.
Item six, other new business if any which the business is posting this agenda.
Seven, staff reports.
Eight, trustee community announcements.
Nine, trust matter communications.
Yes sir.
Ten, executive session consideration and vote to convene into executive session
into the staff room for the purpose of the following agenda items.
Don't need to read all those.
Your motion.
Second.
Dunkel.
Aye.
Parker.
I'll declare us out of executive session at six o'clock
and while executive session session we struck item 11A from the agenda.
We'll go to item 13.
Possible action regarding the sale of 2027B southeast and 2029B southeast.
I make a motion to allow the trust manager to negotiate a potential contract
for the two properties at B southeast.
Second.
Aye.
Item 14, possible action regarding the sale of 411 North Main.
I make a motion to allow the trust manager to negotiate a potential contract
for the properties at 411 North Main.
Substance.
Aye.
Item 15, adjournment.
Motion.
Second.
Aye.